[
    {
        "id": "01",
        "question": "How is the kanji '趣味' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "しゅみ"
    },
    {
        "id": "02",
        "question": "How is the kanji '現金' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "げんきん"
    },
    {
        "id": "03",
        "question": "How is the kanji '日記' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "にっき"
    },
    {
        "id": "04",
        "question": "How is the kanji '集めます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "あつめます"
    },
    {
        "id": "05",
        "question": "How is the kanji '弾きます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "ひきます"
    },
    {
        "id": "06",
        "question": "How is the kanji '洗います' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "あらいます"
    },
    {
        "id": "07",
        "question": "How is the kanji '歌います' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "うたいます"
    },
    {
        "id": "08",
        "question": "How is the kanji '換えます' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "かえます"
    },
    {
        "id": "09",
        "question": "How is the kanji '運転します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "うんてんします"
    },
    {
        "id": "10",
        "question": "How is the kanji '予測します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "よそくします"
    },
    {
        "id": "11",
        "question": "How is the kanji '見学します' read in hiragana?",
        "answer": "けんがくします"
    }
]